Was there ever a point where you were
actually busy or did you kind of kick
back and just discuss with your scouts
as that things were coming? What was
that like?
>> Yeah, I mean it was it was uh I mean it
was really not a lot different with the
exception the phones weren't ringing. We
weren't having a lot of conversations
with other teams. Um a lot of more
discussions about the players and um so
it was um but yeah about as as I
expected. I think it was it went like
how I thought it would go.
>> Have you started talking about trades
with anybody tomorrow? Did you start any
of that today?
>> Not today. I mean, there was some
there's been some talk through the week
just about if, you know, things happen,
you know, we might be open to this or
that. You know, those conversations
happen all week. So, there's been some
of that, but uh not much tonight.
Everybody's kind of concentrated on this
round, I think, more more so than
anything. Those conversations will will
probably pick up tomorrow, tomorrow
afternoon sometime.
>> Ryan, was there anybody taken that you
thought might be there for your first
pick tomorrow?
>> No, I think it really kind of fell. I
mean, it wasn't I mean, there's always,
you know, a couple things. Maybe guys
went a little higher, a little lower
than we expected, but uh um no, just you
know, I didn't think there was any
really major surprises uh like there are
at times. Um but um the board held up,
you know, I felt fairly well um kind of
like we expected it to.
>> Judy, were there any moments at all
where you were making a call? There were
a lot of trades tonight, especially in
the second half. Did you make any calls?
Did you consider it at any point?
>> Not really. Um, you know, John Eric took
care of all that. You know, he was, you
know, trading all over the place. So,
um, which was really cool to see. But
no, um, you know, again, we didn't
really expect, um, for that to happen to
get up into the first round was going to
be uh, quite expensive. Certainly, if it
wouldn't have been, um, we would we may
have entertained it, but that never
really really came.
>> If you watching these guys go off the
board, do you mean for a minute?
I don't say regret. I mean, that's the
wrong word, but
>> no,
>> you you you look at your rivals are
getting better today. Does it or is it
just that, hey, you got Micah Parsons
and that's that's good enough.
>> Yeah, we got better, you know, not not
in with with this particular pick, we
got better a whole year earlier, you
know. So, um so no. Um to answer your
question, I will say and this is is no
different than the other draft when you
when you sit there wherever you're
picking and you're watching good players
come off the board that you've put a lot
of time scouting and you appreciate
their their skill set. That's never fun.
I mean, you always, you know, but um no,
we uh um you know, looking back and and
doing, you know, doing what we did, I
think, um I certainly I don't think
there's any players that were in this
draft that can compete with that one.
>> You if you sit and pick at 52, can you
expect to get what, a guy in the top 30
on your board, or what do you think is
realistic there? Um, I'd have to go back
in there and count them up, but um,
yeah, I mean there's Yeah, I would close
to that, you know. I mean, and we don't,
you know, we don't really stack like one
to 35, right? You know, we it's more
horizontally by position. And so, um, we
don't we don't I know some teams do do
that. We've never ever done that here.
Um, we've never stacked them from one to
whatever. So, um, but we're confident
we're going to get a really good player
if we stick at 52. Um, you know, even if
we move back, we feel really good about
how the board is and that we're going to
get a good player that will help us.
And, um, so, you know, we're excited. I
know I know we're we're all itching
after, you know, sitting through that
today. I think we're all itching to get
after it tomorrow.
>> Two more, please, along along Pete's
lines. Um, Elliott said something
interesting in New England this week. He
said that he thought it's like one
through 20 and then 20 through 50 were
kind of roughly the same type of player
in terms of value. Did you can you say
if you saw the board in a similar way?
And if so, is that a good time to not
have a first round pick that you could
valuewise?
>> You know, Jason, I think that's a I
think that's usually kind of the case um
in most drafts. I think this year might
have fell off a little earlier than
that, you know, maybe 15ish somewhere in
there. Um but yeah, I think um that's
usually kind of the case. Um and we've
obviously picked in the in the mid to
late 20s a lot. Um, but most of the time
I would say one of your top 15 16
usually kind of gets close to you and
you may end up picking that guy anyway.
But um I I do feel like um the players
that um between kind of at the end of
this draft and and where we're going to
be picking tomorrow are very similar.
>> With there still being 19 picks before
you're on the clock, can what happens in
round one have a big impact on your
board or is there still too much space
time to go by?
>> It can. And I don't know if it's going
to change a whole lot about how we
approach it. Um but certainly um you
know at different positions the the
board can can change kind of how maybe
if it doesn't fall exactly how you might
think it it will um it can change. Um I
don't think that's happened for us so
far in this this draft, but um it can
that can happen.
>> With that gap, how how's your feel right
now knowing that there's another what 20
picks that have to wait? Like how how's
your feel right now for what 52 will
look like? Is that something tomorrow?
>> Yeah. I mean, I think obviously we, you
know, all the players that we have um
stacked, you know, we're we're excited
about and uh um but kind of the top of
the second round is always a little bit
chaotic. Everybody has a whole night to
to sleep on things and people get
panicky and then there's all kinds of
trades at times at the top of the second
round. There always has been. Um, so,
um, you know, it's it'll it'll be
interesting how the first 10 to 15
picks, you know, happen tomorrow and
and, um, see if anybody gets close
enough that we feel we may want to go
up. Um, but we feel pretty confident
that we can stick where we're at and
take a good player.
>> Brian, did the run on tackles surprise
you at all? Did it change anything in
terms of where your board is at or what
available?
>> Yeah, actually it didn't. I think we
really expected that. There's no there
was no quarterbacks, you know, there
wasn't a ton of quarterbacks in this
draft. Um it was light at a couple other
positions as well, so we knew the big
guys were going to go fast and they did.
You know, we that that was not a
surprise. Um so, um and you kind of saw
some teams jockeying trying to to get in
position to take him as well.
>> If you if you make a trade tomorrow,
>> I do you prefer or are you looking for
it to be with a pick next year as
opposed to this year?
>> No, I wouldn't say that. No, I think
those picks next year, you know, are
going to be important for us. So, I
wouldn't say that. But, uh, again, if
the right player is there and that's
what it takes, we'll we'll consider it.
Um, but, um, I think I'd prefer to do a
pick this year.